Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  - Guilford County zoning map (Tube 22)
  - Guilford County maps, 1965 (Tube 663)
    Plat Maps
    Abrams Aerial Survey Corporation; Guilford County Planning Department; Guilford County (N.C.)
  - Guilford County maps (Tube 666)
    Topographic Maps
    North Carolina Highway and Public Works Commission; United States Department of the Interior; Guilford County (N.C.)
  - Guilford Technical Community College (1 of 2), 1989 (Tube 165)
    Site plans, master plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Jamestown (N.C.)
  - Guilford Technical Community College (2 of 2), 1989 (Tube 681)
    Mitcham & Associates, PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Jamestown (N.C.)
  - Guilford Technical Community College (Tube 685)
  - Gunter (Harvey) residence (Tube 819)
    Orange County (N.C.)
  - Gut (Ralph and Mary) residence, 1977 (Tube 525)
    Electrical layout, elevation, framing and roof, floor plans, foundation and basement
    Lasater-Hopkins; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Gut (Ralph and Mary) residence, 1976-1977 (Tube 526)
    Study of sun angles, floor plans, elevations, roof framing
  - H. L. Buffaloe & Associates, 1970 (Tube 793)
    Site Development Plan
  - Hackney (Mr. and Mrs. J.A., Jr.) residence, 1965-1967 (Tube 211)
    Planting plan, details - plant list, landscape plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Washington (N.C.)
  - Hackney (Mr. and Mrs. J.A., Jr.) residence, 1967 (Tube 212)
    Details - plant list, site development plan, construction details
  - Hackney (Mr. and Mrs. T.J.) residence (Tube 263)
    Landscape development plan, construction details
  - Hackney (Mr. and Mrs. T.J.) residence (1 of 2), 1976 (Tube 298)
    Site staking, details, plant list, planting notes
  - Hackney (Mr. and Mrs. T.J.) residence (2 of 2), 1976 (Tube 303)
  - Hafer (Gene and Holly) residence, 1978-1979 (Tube 777)
    Landscape development
  - Hafer (Gene and Holly) residence, 1979 (Tube 778)
  - Halifax County Consolidated High School, 1970 (Tube 321)
    Schematic site plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Halifax County (N.C.)
  - Halifax County Courthouse: Additions, 1962-1964 (Tube 245)
    Davis Charles C. Jr. AIA; Halifax (N.C.)
  - Hall (Jane) residence (Tube 212)
  - Halstead (Bill and Martha) residence, 1989-1991 (Tube 38)
  - Halstead (Bill and Martha) residence, 1991 (Tube 40)
  - Hamilton (Dr. and Mrs. R.P.) residence, 1964 (Tube 211)
    Preliminary plan
  - Hammocks Beach: "The Hammocks" Resort Community, 1968-1985 (Tube 335)
    Memorial chapel and meditation garden, conference center and resort area, master plan, classroom teachers development
    Bell Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Swansboro (N.C.)
  - Hammocks Beach: "The Hammocks" Resort Community, 1965-1985 (Tube 334)
    Property map, location maps, duplex cottage units, master plan, marina, sound villas, golf villas, assembly, lodge, banquet hall
    Bell Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Swansboro (N.C.)
  - Hanes (Mr. and Mrs. Frank Borden) residence (1 of 4), 1976 (Tube 283)
  - Hanes (Mr. and Mrs. Frank Borden) residence (2 of 4), 1976 (Tube 298)
    Master development plan, landscape development plan
  - Hanes (Mr. and Mrs. Frank Borden) residence (3 of 4), 1976 (Tube 303)
  - Hanes (Mr. and Mrs. Frank Borden) residence (4 of 4), 1976 (Tube 458)
  - Hardy (Mr. and Mrs. David) residence, 1968 (Tube 802)
    Glave & Newman Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Wilson (N.C.)
  - Hardy (Mr. and Mrs. David) residence, 1966 (Tube 805)
    Landscape plan, planting plan
  - Harlon Companies: Mill Valley Apartments (Tube 539)
    Preliminary Offsite Wastewater Plan
    Black & Veatch; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Harris (Mr. and Mrs. Clyde P., Jr.) residence (1 of 2), 1979 (Tube 48)
  - Harris (Mr. and Mrs. Clyde P., Jr.) residence (2 of 2), 1979 (Tube 729)
    Construction Details, Planting/Construction Details, Overall Planting and Plans, Overall Staking, South Elevation Showing Carport Addition
  - Harris (Mr. and Mrs. Clyde P., Jr.) residence (Tube 778)
  - Harris (Mr. and Mrs. Clyde P., Jr.) residence, 1978 (Tube 777)
  - Harris (Mr. and Mrs. J.M.) residence, 1968 (Tube 212)
    Garage additions
  - Harris (Mrs. Lola H.) residence, 1987 (Tube 717)
  - Harry (Dr. and Mrs. J.M.) residence, 1966 (Tube 212)
  - Hartford Hills, 1986 (Tube 715)
    Pool Deck Addition, Preliminary Design Development, Site Plan
  - Harvey (Mr. and Mrs. W.S.) residence, 1971 (Tube 494)
  - Haworth (Mr. Byron) property, 1978 (Tube 744)
    James C. Fulbright & Associates; High Point (N.C.)
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church, 1994 (Flatfolder 19)
    Master landscape plan, master site development
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church (1 of 3), 1996-2002 (Tube 434)
    Planting plan, staking/grading plan, construction details, irrigation plan, grading details
    Alpha Design Group; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church (2 of 3), 1996-2002 (Tube 435)
    Master site development, planting plan, grading, drainage, erosion, construction details, grading details
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church (3 of 3), 1996-2002 (Tube 436)
    Master site development, building section, floor plans, elevations, planting plan, grading, drainage, erosion
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Alpha Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church, 1981-1997 (Tube 122)
    Sign; pre-school building, proposed landscape garden of memories, boundary and topographic survey
    Bell Design Group; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church, 1977-1997 (Tube 121)
    Proposed parking area, proposed landscape design of memorial garden, sign
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Hayes Barton United Methodist Church (Tube 552)
    Notes, Rough Site Notes
  - Hayes (Virginia) property, 1982 (Tube 713)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Wilson County (N.C.)
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores, 1982 (Tube 456)
    Master Plan, Interiors, Grading & Sedimentation Control Plan
    Bell Design Group; Willis James B. Jr.; Morehead City (N.C.)
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores, 1982-1983 (Tube 757)
    Vicinity map, staking plan, grading plan, site development
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores, 1983 (Tube 282)
    Willis James B. Jr.; Bell Design Group; Morehead City (N.C.)
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores (1 of 3), 1983-1985 (Tube 504)
    Marina Relocation, Vicinity Map, Master Plan, Staking Plan, Major Revision Concept Buildings, Birdie Court, Site Plans
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores (2 of 3), 1983-1985 (Tube 505)
    Floor plans, Site Plans, Elevations
  - The Haystacks at Newport Shores (3 of 3), 1983-1985 (Tube 506)
    Site Plans, Elevation, Parcels to be released
  - Hazard (Mr. and Mrs. Joseph) property, 1973 (Tube 688)
    Bell Design Group; Tribble Michael Architect; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Headwaters of Crabtree, 1982 (Tube 715)
    Land Use Study, Topographic Plan
  - Hemphill (Mr. and Mrs. Samuel M.) residence, 1969 (Tube 851)
    Site Plan, Site Details, Planting Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Henderson (Doug and Cathie) residence, 1987 (Tube 713)
    Site Development Plans, Planting Plan, Irrigation Plan, Site Development Plans
  - Hermes (Mr. and Mrs. Julius) residence (1 of 3), 1978 (Tube 729)
    Plans for Pool/Deck Construction, Overall Planting, Site Plan
    Bell Design Group; Martinsville (Va.)
  - Hermes (Mr. and Mrs. Julius) residence (2 of 3), 1978 (Tube 779)
    Details for pool/deck construction
  - Hermes (Mr. and Mrs. Julius) residence (3 of 3), 1978 (Tube 780)
  - Herring (Dr. and Mrs. W.I.) residence, 1965 (Tube 211)
    Schematic site study
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Oxenfeld & Newkirk; Clinton (N.C.)
  - Herring (Dr. and Mrs. W.I.) residence (Tube 212)
  - Hertford Village (Tube 710)
  - Hickory High School, 1968 (Tube 781)
    Site study plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Hickory Architects Collaborative; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Hickory High School (Tube 779)
    Hickory Architects Collaborative; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Hickory High School: New building for Hickory Administrative School Unit, 1970 (Tube 767)
    Staking Plans, Site Construction Details, Site Plans, Overall Staking Plans, Storm Drainage Plan, Detailed Staking Plans, Revised Preliminary Site Plan
    Hickory Architects Collaborative; Richard C. Bell Associates; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Hickory Hills on Lake Hickory (1 of 2), 1973 (Tube 35)
    Bell Design Group; Alexander County (N.C.)
  - Hickory Hills on Lake Hickory (2 of 2), 1973 (Tube 34)
    Alexander County (N.C.)
  - High Point Bank & Trust Co. (1 of 2), 1984 (Tube 713)
    Auto Access and Parking Studies
    Allred & Mercer Architects, Inc.; Bell Design Group; High Point (N.C.)
  - High Point Bank & Trust Co. (2 of 2), 1984 (Tube 714)
    Bell Design Group; Allred & Mercer Architects, Inc.; High Point (N.C.)
  - High Point University (1 of 2), 1994 (Tube 294)
    Landscape development plan, grading/drainage/sedimentation and erosion control, aerial photograph, topographic survey
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Allred & Mercer Architects, Inc.; High Point (N.C.)
  - High Point University (2 of 2), 1994 (Tube 295)
    Landscape development plan, demolition plan, staking plan, grading/drainage/sediment and erosion control, planting plan, irrigation plan, lighting plan, topographic survey, master campus plan
  - High Rise Apartment Building for the Elderly: P.H.A. Project, NC 13.6 for Housing Authority, 1965-1966 (Tube 52)
    M.A. Ham Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Highland House: Convalescent Nursing Center (1 of 2), 1968 (Tube 785)
  - Highland House: Convalescent Nursing Center (2 of 2), 1968 (Tube 850)
    Grading and Storm Drainage, Planting Plan
  - Hill Building: Research Triangle Institute Building No. 10, 1997 (Tube 465)
    Landscape Plans, Grading Plans, Irrigation, Site Plans
  - Hill (Watts and Mary) residence (1 of 2), 1991 (Tube 507)
    Master Plan, Landscape Plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Beaufort (N.C.)
  - Hill (Watts and Mary) residence (2 of 2), 1991 (Tube 716)
    Master Plan and Landscape Plan, Details of Construction, Lighting Plan, Irrigation Plan, Planting Plan, Staking Plan
  - Hillside Gardens (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Proposed Site Plans
  - Hillside Gardens (Tube 445)
    Proposed Site Plan
  - Hillside Gardens (Tube 834)
    Proposed Site Plan, Elevations, Site Plan
  - Hilltop Home (Tube 713)
    Landscape Development Plan, Gazebo Details, Grading Plan, Planting Plan, Staking Plan, Garden Wish list
  - Hillyer Memorial Christian Church: Proposed office building, 1965 (Tube 182)
    Schematic study
  - Historic Newkirk House Restoration, 1975 (Tube 252)
    Bell Design Group; Wilmington (N.C.)
  - Historic Newkirk House Restoration and Visitors Center for Industrial Sales Co., Inc., 1975 (Tube 747)
    Construction Details, Site Plans, Staking and Wall Details, Elevations
  - Hodges (Governor and Mrs. Luther) residence, 1972-1973 (Tube 48)
    Overall site plan
  - Hodges (Governor and Mrs. Luther) residence, 1965 (Tube 212)
  - Hodges (Mr. and Mrs. John) residence (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 211)
  - Hodges (Mr. and Mrs. John) residence (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 212)
    Construction plan
  - Holder (Mrs. Fredrick) residence, 1967 (Tube 850)
    Landscape Plan, Schematic Site Plan, Schematic Site Study, Landscape Plan
    Clemmer-Horton-Bush Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Holding (Mr. and Mrs. Frank B.) residence (1 of 2), 1974 (Tube 495)
    Details, site plan
    Bell Design Group; Smithfield (N.C.)
  - Holding (Mr. and Mrs. Frank B.) residence (2 of 2), 1974 (Tube 493)
    Site plan, planting plan, terrace details, grading plan
  - Holiday Acres: Master plan, 1965 (Tube 51)
    Dr. and Mrs. R.P. Hamilton, developers
  - Holisinger (Bob and Judy), 1989 (Tube 715)
    Preliminary Landscape Plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Burlington (N.C.)
  - Holly Park (Tube 347)
  - Holly's Ridge: Blanton (Bill and Holly) property, 1985 (Tube 695)
  - Holt (Mr. and Mrs. J. R.) residence (1 of 2), 1969 (Tube 785)
    Planting Plan, Staking Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Mebane (N.C.)
  - Holt (Mr. and Mrs. J. R.) residence (2 of 2), 1969 (Tube 802)
    Planting plan, details, plant list, landscape development plan
  - Holy Trinity Episcopal Church (1 of 2), 1999 (Tube 229)
    Site improvement plan
  - Holy Trinity Episcopal Church (2 of 2), 1999 (Tube 231)
    Landscape planting plan, grading, drainage, erosion
  - Home Federal Savings and Loan Association (Tube 264)
  - Home Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1974 (Tube 5)
  - Home Federal Savings and Loan Association: Farmville office (Tube 4)
    Bell Design Group; Farmville (N.C.)
  - Home Federal Savings and Loan Association: Hardee Road office (Tube 4)
  - Home Office Building: Branch Bank and Trust Company, 1970 (Tube 508)
  - Hood (Thornton and Louise) residence, 1990 (Tube 718)
    Landscape Plan and Details
    Willis Architects; Bell Design Group; Morehead City (N.C.)
  - Hope Valley Property for Southland Associates, 1973 (Tube 514)
    Land Use Survey
  - Horn (Mr. and Mrs. Claude R.) residence, 1976-1977 (Tube 299)
    Grading and storm drainage, planting, plant list, landscape development plan
    Bell Design Group; Mocksville (N.C.)
  - Horn (Mr. and Mrs. Claude R., Jr.) residence, 1977 (Tube 303)
  - Horton (Mr. and Mrs. Marvin V.) residence, 1972 (Tube 850)
    Site Plan, Preliminary Landscape Plan, Alternate Preliminary Landscape Plan
    Bell Design Group; Tarboro (N.C.)
  - Hospitality Suites Raleigh Corporate Center, 1985-1989 (Tube 825)
    Master Plans, Site Plans, Keynoted Information, Paving Plan
    Jenkins-Peer Architects PA; John A. Edwards & Company, Consulting Engineers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Hotel/Conference Center, 1989 (Flatfolder 20)
    Site plan, bird's eye view, longitudinal section
  - Hotel/Conference Center: Proche Management, Inc., 1989 (Tube 501)
    Bird's eye view: Hotel/Conference Center Looking South-West, Perspectives, Elevations
    Cook Jerry A.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - House S-3515 (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 55)
  - House S-3515 (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 871)
    Elevations, Site Plan, Second Floor Plan and Details, First Floor Plan
  - Housing Authority of the City of Durham: McDouglad Terrace (Tube 440)
    Site Plan Documenting Soil Erosion
  - Housing Authority of the City of Durham: P.H.A. Project NC 13-6, 1965-1970 (Tube 851)
    Supplementary #5, Landscape Lighting Study, Tree Fencing Plan, High Rise Apartment Building for the Elderly: Schematic Site Plan and Preliminary Site Plan; Supplementary #3, Revision Drawing "A," Supplementary Drawing #2
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Carr, Harrison, Pruden & DePasquale; M.A. Ham Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Housing Authority of the City of Durham: Project Numbers NC 13-6, NC 13-8, 1965 (Tube 52)
    Carr, Harrison, Pruden & DePasquale; Durham (N.C.)
  - Housing Authority of the City of High Point: Low rental housing project, 1972 (Tube 304)
    Lot grading schematic, site development plan
    George Connor & Associates; High Point (N.C.)
  - Housing Authority of the City of Raleigh: Housing for the Elderly, 1969 (Tube 281)
    Guy E. Crampton and Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Housing Authority of the City of Raleigh: Housing for the Elderly, 1967-1969 (Tube 500)
    Planting notes, Alternate plans, Site plans
    Guy E. Crampton and Associates; Bell Richard C. 1928-; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Housing Authority of Durham: Housing Project N.C. 13-11, 1969 (Tube 52)
    Schematic plan
  - Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge and Restaurant (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 247)
    Drainage plan, detail plan, planting plan
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Roanoke Island (N.C.)
  - Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge and Restaurant (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 248)
    Detail plan, construction details, planting list, planting plan
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Roanoke Rapids (N.C.)
  - Howard residence (1 of 2), 1997 (Tube 234)
    Floor plans, details, elevations
    Tate J. Knox IV Architect
  - Howard residence (2 of 2), 1997 (Tube 235)
  - Howard (Chip and Rickie) property and residence (1 of 2), 1998 (Tube 79)
    Staking plan, planting plan, lighting plan,
  - Howard (Chip and Rickie) property and residence (2 of 2), 1998 (Tube 80)
    Master landscape plan, grading and drainage plan, revised site plan, staking plan, planting plan, lighting plan
  - Hubbard (Mr. and Mrs. R. L.) residence, 1979 (Tube 729)
    Site Plans, Planting Plan
  - Hudson Memorial Presbyterian Church, 1965 (Tube 713)
    Planting Plan, Site Plan, Staking Plan
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. I. N.) residence, 1959 (Tube 447)
    Plant List, Site Plans
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. James O.) residence, 1979 (Tube 48)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. James O.) residence (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 283)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. James O.) residence (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 777)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. James O.) residence (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Tube 778)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. James O.) residence (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Tube 779)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. Karl, Jr.) residence, 1963 (Tube 805)
  - Hudson (Mr. and Mrs. Karl, Jr.) residence, 1968 (Tube 802)
    Site plan, construction details, planting plan, landscape development
  - Hutaff (Miss Dorothy) residence, 1967 (Tube 851)
  - I-85 Bypass Corridor, 1992 (Tube 21)
    Study showing the interchange connecting the I-85 Bypass Corridor with the Eastern/Northern Loop at McConnell Road
  - IBM: Employee activity and fitness center (Flatfolder 18)
    Site master plan, site schemes
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Burnstudio Architects
  - Imperial Center: Winchester Place, 1998 (Tube 223)
  - Jacob Swamp Project (Tube 845)
    Landscape Management Plan, Schedule of Drawings, Key Plan, Site Plans
    United States Soil Conservation Service; Bell Design Group; Robeson County (N.C.)
  - Jamestown Area (Tube 866)
    North Carolina Division of Highways Photogrammetric Unit; Guilford County (N.C.)
  - Jamesville School (Tube 58)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Martin County (N.C.)
  - Jansen (Wolfgang) Litchfield Plantation, 1969 (Tube 8)
  - Jansen (Wolfgang) residence, 1969 (Tube 458)
    Site Plan Development
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Litchfield Plantation (S.C.)
  - Jansen (Wolfgang) residence (Tube 17)
  - Jefferson Gardens Apartment (Tube 890)
  - Jefferson Pilot Corporation: Sedgefield property, 1992 (Tube 22)
    Land-Use Study Showing Impact of Proposed Corridors
  - Jefferson Sugg Builder: 2409 Tri-Level, 1964 (Tube 528)
    Truss schedule, floor plans
  - Johnson (Mr. and Mrs. Earl, Sr.) residence, 1969-1970 (Tube 8)
  - Johnson (Mr. and Mrs. Eric) residence (Tube 458)
  - Johnston (Dr. and Mrs. Mac) residence, 1976 (Tube 784)
    Preliminary landscape development, grading, details, planting, details, plant list
  - Johnston (John and Gretchen) residence (1 of 2), 1984 (Tube 12)
  - Johnston (John and Gretchen) residence (2 of 2), 1984 (Tube 640)
    Landscape design scheme 2
  - Johnston (John and Gretchen) residence (Tube 644)
  - Joklik (Mr. and Mrs. Wolfgang Karl) residence (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 458)
    Grading and Staking
    Bell Design Group; Durham County (N.C.)
  - Joklik (Mr. and Mrs. Wolfgang Karl) residence (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 785)
    Planting Plan (Rear), Planting Plan (Front), Grading Information, Grading
  - Joklik (Mr. and Mrs. Wolfgang Karl) residence, 1977-1978 (Tube 783)
    Staking, construction details, planting plan, landscape design
  - Jones and Richards residence, 1969 (Tube 8)
  - Jones (Alan and Orrell) residence (1 of 2), 1986 (Tube 818)
    Landscape plan, irrigation, lighting, details
  - Jones (Alan and Orrell) residence (2 of 2), 1986 (Tube 819)
    Garden plan, garden details
  - Jones (Mr. and Mrs. B.A.) residence, 1969 (Tube 17)
    Pool plan and details
    Edwin E. Mogilnicki and Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Jones (Mr. and Mrs. Drewery J.) residence, 1966 (Tube 458)
  - Jordan (Gene and Carolyn) residence (1 of 2), 1995 (Tube 818)
  - Jordan (Gene and Carolyn) residence (2 of 2), 1995 (Tube 819)
  - Joyner Farm, 1998 (Flatfolder 17)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Louisburg (N.C.)
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (1 of 2), 1998 (Flatfolder 19)
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (2 of 2), 1998 (Tube 441)
    Plans and Elevations; Detailed Floor Plans; Plan and Elevation; Preliminary Master Plan; Lot and Staking Plan; House Plan and Elevations; Site Plans
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (1 of 4), 1999 (Tube 108)
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (2 of 4), 1999 (Tube 109)
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (3 of 4), 1999 (Tube 287)
  - Katz (Barry, Belinda, and Noah) residence (4 of 4), 1999 (Tube 291)
    Site plan, floor plans, elevations, construction details
  - Kavanagh (John) undeveloped land, 1988 (Tube 663)
    Revised Master Plan
    Evans Engineering, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Kelley residence, 2002 (Tube 487)
    Elevations, floor plans, roof framing
  - Kelley (Scott) residence (1 of 2), 2003
    Topographic surveys, site plans
    Bell-Glazener-Jenkins Planning; Philip Post and Associates Inc.; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Kelley (Scott) residence (2 of 2), 2003 (Tube 893)
  - Kelly (Dr. and Mrs. Scott) Estate (Tube 231)
    Bell-Glazener-Jenkins Planning; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Kelly (Dr. and Mrs. Scott) Estate, 2003 (Tube 322)
  - Kerr (Mr. and Mrs. Banks D.) residence (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 477)
  - Kerr (Mr. and Mrs. Banks D.) residence (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 478)
    Landscape plans, construction details
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (1 of 3), 2000 (Tube 678)
    Exterior elevations, basement construction plan, first floor construction plan
    Hall-Davenport Associates, PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Durham (N.C.)
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (2 of 3), 2000 (Tube 131)
    Coversheet, site plan, project notes, floor plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Hall-Davenport Associates, PA; Durham (N.C.)
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (3 of 3), 2000 (Tube 133)
    Conceptual landscape development plan; floor plan
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (1 of 7), 2001 (Flatfolder 13)
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (2 of 7), 2001 (Tube 404)
    Cover sheet, project notes, basement construction plan, first floor construction plan, second floor construction plan, roof plan, exterior elevations
    Hall-Davenport Associates, PA; Durham (N.C.)
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (3 of 7), 2001 (Tube 405)
    Building sections, wall sections, details, window schedule, door schedule
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (4 of 7), 2001 (Tube 406)
    Finish schedule, trim details, interior elevations, mill work details
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (5 of 7), 2001 (Tube 676)
    Planting plan, storm water plan, existing conditions, demolition plan, overall master plan, staking plan, grading plan
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (6 of 7), 2001 (Tube 677)
    Lighting plan, construction details, irrigation plan, aerial photograph
  - Kessman (Nancy and Alan) residence (7 of 7), 2001 (Tube 278)
    Staking and grading plan, erosion control, storm water plan
  - Kilgore (Mr. and Mrs. Ben) residence, 1973-1984 (Tube 283)
  - Kilgore (Mr. and Mrs. Ben) residence, 1972 (Tube 291)
    Details, elevations, planting plan
  - Kindell (Pat) residence (1 of 2), 1980 (Tube 494)
    Bell Design Group; Morehead City (N.C.)
  - Kindell (Pat) residence (2 of 2), 1980 (Tube 493)
    Elevations
  - King (Robert and Renee) residence (1 of 2), 1981 (Tube 494)
  - King (Robert and Renee) residence (2 of 2), 1981 (Tube 493)